Jonathan Guzman

UX Designer

www.jguzman.design jon.guzman@gmail.com 510.333.4597 • SF/Bay Area, CA

SUMMARY

I am an empathetic designer well-versed in creating intuitive interfaces. I rarely shy away from a challenge and I am a tenacious problem solver. A former teacher, DJ, and Apple Genius, I use all my unique experiences to create products people love to use. I put people before products and I am proud of it.

SKILLS

Problem Solving Visual Design Interaction Design Product Design UX Design Storyboarding Information Architecture Branding Typography Content Strategy Wireframing Prototyping User Research **User Testing** Cross-functional collaboration Web Development Spanish & French

TOOLS

Figma
Sketch
Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator
InVision
Usability Hub
Lucidchart
Bynder & Webdam
Maze
Github
HTML, CSS & Javascript

LATEST PROJECTS

Method MI | UX Design & Website Deployment

Method Media Intelligence is a leader in advertising fraud detection technology. My role was to reorganize and wireframe their new website to help turn visitors into customers.

GameChanger | UX Design, Branding & Visual Design

GameChanger is a marketplace app for gamers to barter items. My focus was to create a mobile interface that lets gamers find what they're looking for quickly, easily, and with no money exchanged.

Stash | UX Design, Branding & Visual Design

Stash is an online cloud storage application made with a millennial audience in mind. I created a robust web interface that allowed people to store, share, and organize files they care about most.

EXPERIENCE

UX Designer Shion Studio | Remote

Sep 2019 - present

- Implement Shion creative team assets into my designs and informational hierarchy strategy
- Meet with stakeholders to translate feedback into tangible deliverables
- Increased Method Media Intelligence website engagement by 22% resulting in an increased demand for product demos
- Deploy websites and custom code to ensure sites are functioning properly

IT Ops Helpdesk Technician Pinterest | San Francisco

July 2019 - present

- Collaborate across teams to reinvent our knowledge base articles
- Adhere to brand considerations while executing new design template within Atlassian's Confluence product
- Decreased Helpdesk traffic by nearly 20% within 3 months of new site launch
- Support hardware and software requests

Design Apprentice Bloc | Remote

Sep 2017 - Jun 2019

- Engaged in all parts of the design process—from ideating solutions to producing fully-functional prototypes
- Sought frequent feedback from design mentors, colleagues, and design reviews
- Crafted engaging copy, organized content, memorable branding, and functional web development for several projects.

EDUCATION

Bloc | UX Design and Front End Development Program UC Berkeley | BA Psychology w/ Minor in Education